{"data":[{"question":"Kurt's office is ____ the second floor.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Our company has stores _____ 12 states.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"My office is____the second floor.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"The conference is _____ 6 June.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"What are you doing _____ the weekend?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+  in: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ at: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ on: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Why are you standing _____ one foot?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Use on with street name","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"David bought his car _____ 1998.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Do not walk _____ the grass.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"You'll have to excuse me. I'm going to grab a cup of coffee _____ Starbucks before work.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"John lives _____ 357 North Highland Drive.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"}]}